[{"answer": "Not that we know of", "docId": "Metro.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Maybe we can get a throw phone in there", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Really?! He's a wonderful guy. He makes two million a year, and he worships me", "docId": "Metro.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "You worship yourself", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "You worship yourself", "docId": "Metro.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " And a car", "docId": "Metro.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You know you've got nothing but cars down there in impound", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I've rarely shot anyone", "docId": "Metro.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " I know", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "God damn it! I still needed to case that fucking store. It's too risky to show my face now", "docId": "Metro.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Leave town? They're going to know me in fucking my friend now!...  They got over ten million in jewels in that place. That's freedom, man. I could go anywhere I want", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "With your qualifications you must have had a lot of offers. Why here", "docId": "Metro.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You don't like that place", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "How did you like that place", "docId": "Metro.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You're a real excitable sort, aren't you", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You're a real excitable sort, aren't you", "docId": "Metro.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I grew up in that place... Crossed the that place and here I was.  So you're looking for", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I don't really like to drink", "docId": "Metro.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Well, if I have to, I have to", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "She's going to come here when she graduates and then we're gonna get married", "docId": "Metro.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " No, no, no...  She's from that place", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "She grow up in that place, too", "docId": "Metro.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Oh,", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Oh,", "docId": "Metro.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Every couple of months, huh", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "That's a lot of commitment. I admire that", "docId": "Metro.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "No. Actually I think it's fucking crazy, I don't know if I could do it", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "If you want to be a successful negotiator, you've got to learn to lie", "docId": "Metro.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Get good at it", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Metro.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "So why would you hesitate to lie to save lives", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "See the favorite? Tail up. Washy. He doesn't want to run today. Cross him off... Now the Six looks good. On his toes. Coat shiny. This traine", "docId": "Metro.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I have three words for you... E", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "That's okay. That's his style", "docId": "Metro.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "To run late", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "And what about the ones you don't save", "docId": "Metro.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "And what if you can't live with it", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "No, no, see what I'm sayin' is, I've got the", "docId": "Metro.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Hey, hey, I got shit on the outside. I got somebody cashing it in for me and", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I mean I said this trip should be a 'roadtest'", "docId": "Metro.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I'm talking about... What are you talking about", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "I'm talking about me 'n' you stripping down on this beach and gettin' you know... 'naked in that place'", "docId": "Metro.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "You thought I was talking about getting married?", "qsentId": 44}]